Guide to the Big Band Arrangements Collection, 1990-2017 SC.2017.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Three Way Arrangements, VII.
  - My Blue Heaven (Box 51, Folder 318)
  - Nearness of You (Box 51, Folder 75)
  - New Kind of Love (Box 51, Folder 74)
  - Oh But I Do (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Oh You Beautiful Doll, Vocal Band (Box 51, Folder 314)
  - Old Cape Cod (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Over the Rainbow (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Park Avenue (Box 51, Folder 106)
  - Petticoats of Portugal (Box 51, Folder 90)
  - Pretending (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Red Sails (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - Ritmando Cha Cha (Box 51, Folder 123)
  - Rose Room (Box 51, Folder 119)
  - Roseanne (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - Say It's Wonderful (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Sentimental Reasons (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - September Song (Box 51, Folder 69)
  - Seven Come Eleven (Box 51, Folder 88)
  - Shangri-La (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Should I (Box 51, Folder 125)
  - Skirts (Box 51, Folder 132)
  - Sleepy Time Gal (Box 51, Folder 126)
  - Speak Low (Box 51, Folder 108)
  - St. Louis Blues (Box 51, Folder 138)
  - Stardust (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - Struttin' With Some Barbecue (Box 51, Folder 137)
  - Sunday Kind of Love (Box 51, Folder 81)
  - Sugar to Tea (Box 51, Folder 128)
  - Sweet and Gentle (Box 51, Folder 113)
  - Take a Chance on Love (Box 51, Folder 322)
  - Take the "A" Train (Box 51, Folder 317)
  - Talk of the Town (Box 51, Folder 71)
  - That Thing (Box 51, Folder 315)
  - The Continental (Box 51, Folder 310)
  - The End of a Love Affair (Lenny Mehal) (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - The Man I Love (Box 51, Folder 82)
  - The Sound of Music (Box 51, Folder 77)
  - The Whole World is Singing My Song (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Three Little Words (Box 51, Folder 301)
  - To You My Love (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Trumpet Cha Cha (Box 51, Folder 110)
  - Viva Amor (Box 51, Folder 114)
  - Vem Vem (Box 51, Folder 105)
  - Watch Your Step (Box 51, Folder 122)
  - Wedding Bells (Box 51, Folder 133)
  - When the Saints Go Marching In (Box 51, Folder 116)
  - When the Saints Go Marching In (Box 51, Folder 134)
  - When Your Love Has Gone (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Why Try to Change Me Now (Box 51, Folder 64)
  - Wish You Were Here (Box 51, Folder 107)
  - Yours (Box 51, Folder 100)